<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on bulletprooftoupee</title>
    <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on bulletprooftoupee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 23:56:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Bad List</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/another-bad-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 23:56:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/another-bad-list/</guid>
      <description>A summer project: I&amp;rsquo;ve been having a rough go of it lately, trouble w/ work, difficulty parenting, struggling w/ imposter syndrome. In order to be healtier and happier, the efforts to achieve happiness and fulfillment are tied directly to overcoming obstacles. Getting work done is a good way to start, spending more time w/ kids and generally being more productive I think is good way to combat feelings of worthlessness and depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dryp: A remote garden manager</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/dryp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 09:07:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/dryp/</guid>
      <description>This project is to fulfill a couple ends. The first is purely for professional development and add new and relevant work to my portfolio. The idea is to create a &amp;ldquo;mock&amp;rdquo; product and run it through from basic concept to a finished product complete w/ screen designs, work flows, functional and technical specs. While it may never see the light of day in terms of a real, functional product, I think that, as a project demonstrating the breadth of my abilities it will be apparent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Library Life</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/library-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 14:14:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/library-life/</guid>
      <description> A list of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished and worked on at NYPL  Collaborated w/ Second Storey on design concepts and implementation  overall site information architecture home page across viewport sizes blog concepts book lists staff pics best books library &amp;amp; librarian book lists basic site wide search (beta search) landing pages  Work closely w/ front end engineers, content creators Worked on developing a functional style guide (Design Tool Kit) Worked closely entire team to address site wide Accessibility issues Aligned Design practice to mirror engineering practice  designing in code use of git to version design  Vetting design &amp;amp; UX assumptions with wireframe prototypes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning the New BPT</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/planning-the-new-bpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 15:32:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/planning-the-new-bpt/</guid>
      <description>Thinking about how this site will be structured is all fine and good, but what about the content? Beyond these ramblings, I think it would be good to present a better picture of what kind content will be in this site.
I don&amp;rsquo;t mind terribly the way the old site is, with portfolio centric content. I do plan on integrating more coding experiments as I improve my skills with Javascript (and any other languages I might be interested in&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m looking at you Processing and Python).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Fluid Type</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/why-fluid-type/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 08:09:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/why-fluid-type/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been obsessed with fluid type for a while now.
 It makes sense to decouple from device based viewport sizes  follows the principle of: Make layout improvements when the it looks bad at a certain viewport size   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Gulp and Others</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/getting-gulp-and-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 22:29:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/getting-gulp-and-others/</guid>
      <description>What do you need gulp.js for anyway? The whole point is to learn a few things, where to start? I suppose with fundamentals. I&amp;rsquo;ve been avoiding JS for years. It was in the early 2000&amp;rsquo;s when I came across a JS book and I did some examples and ran through the chapters. None of it stuck. I blamed it on poor writing and inadequate documentation. Really, though, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t grok some of the concepts and gave up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Hugo Up and Running</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/getting-hugo-up-and-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 22:12:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/getting-hugo-up-and-running/</guid>
      <description> bungling the config file  just use a theme  plan out the next iterations  porting the drupal site?  headache to be sure  start simple: small log of days activities writing about learning stuff  cnc struggle w/ js amassing books but not reading with the intent of thorough attention i&amp;rsquo;d like to rectify  what is the portfolio really looking like these days  code quality is probably just as important as design   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>