<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bulletprooftoupee.com | The personal site of Ricardo E. Galvez on bulletprooftoupee</title>
    <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bulletprooftoupee.com | The personal site of Ricardo E. Galvez on bulletprooftoupee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 17:03:37 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Svg Icons</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/portfolio/svg-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 17:03:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/portfolio/svg-icons/</guid>
      <description> DGX Icon works here yo </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nypl Blogs</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/portfolio/nypl-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 00:05:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/portfolio/nypl-blogs/</guid>
      <description> the cat is meowing This Image is the supplied caption yeah...  This Image is the supplied caption yeah...   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Bad List</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/another-bad-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 23:56:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/another-bad-list/</guid>
      <description>A summer project: I&amp;rsquo;ve been having a rough go of it lately, trouble w/ work, difficulty parenting, struggling w/ imposter syndrome. In order to be healtier and happier, the efforts to achieve happiness and fulfillment are tied directly to overcoming obstacles. Getting work done is a good way to start, spending more time w/ kids and generally being more productive I think is good way to combat feelings of worthlessness and depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dryp: A remote garden manager</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/dryp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 09:07:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/dryp/</guid>
      <description>This project is to fulfill a couple ends. The first is purely for professional development and add new and relevant work to my portfolio. The idea is to create a &amp;ldquo;mock&amp;rdquo; product and run it through from basic concept to a finished product complete w/ screen designs, work flows, functional and technical specs. While it may never see the light of day in terms of a real, functional product, I think that, as a project demonstrating the breadth of my abilities it will be apparent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canvas Workings</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/experiments/canvas-workings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 14:59:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/experiments/canvas-workings/</guid>
      <description>We want to put the canvas as a whole big background image&amp;hellip; It might be prudent or useful to put a custom scss shortcode here as well?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning the New BPT</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/planning-the-new-bpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 15:32:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/planning-the-new-bpt/</guid>
      <description>Thinking about how this site will be structured is all fine and good, but what about the content? Beyond these ramblings, I think it would be good to present a better picture of what kind content will be in this site.
I don&amp;rsquo;t mind terribly the way the old site is, with portfolio centric content. I do plan on integrating more coding experiments as I improve my skills with Javascript (and any other languages I might be interested in&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m looking at you Processing and Python).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Fluid Type</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/why-fluid-type/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 08:09:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/why-fluid-type/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been obsessed with fluid type for a while now.
 It makes sense to decouple from device based viewport sizes  follows the principle of: Make layout improvements when the it looks bad at a certain viewport size   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Canvas Experiment Pt 6</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/experiments/a-canvas-experiment-pt-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 18:24:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/experiments/a-canvas-experiment-pt-6/</guid>
      <description>This is moving right along. Faithful readers will now see I have created a custom Hugo short-code that allows us to easily embed canvas elements into a markdown file. Yeah. I&amp;rsquo;ve also conimaged Gulp to concatenate and uglify the javascript so we can use multiple project files to work from but we serve a nice minified and concatenated javascript file. Next up&amp;hellip; lets do the same minifiying to our css shall we?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 13:48:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/about/about/</guid>
      <description> Contact  phone masked email address  Experience Stuff needed:  download this resume print css for this page head shot? (yuk)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Experience</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/experiments/my-new-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 13:46:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/experiments/my-new-experience/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been obsessed w/ fluid type for a year. So this year, along w/ all of my other front end chopping I plan on chopping. Fluid type will be getting under the belts&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Gulp and Others</title>
      <link>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/getting-gulp-and-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 22:29:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://proto.bulletprooftoupee.com/posts/getting-gulp-and-others/</guid>
      <description>What do you need gulp.js for anyway? The whole point is to learn a few things, where to start? I suppose with fundamentals. I&amp;rsquo;ve been avoiding JS for years. It was in the early 2000&amp;rsquo;s when I came across a JS book and I did some examples and ran through the chapters. None of it stuck. I blamed it on poor writing and inadequate documentation. Really, though, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t grok some of the concepts and gave up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>